Location Station Owners/Managers Interviews
Location Station Owners/Managers Interviews
2001-2002
Marc, David.
30 items
Interviews, mostly by David Marc, of owners and managers of local radio and television stations
5390533
Biographical History
David Marc is an author, editor, and teacher specializing in communication and mass media. He earned his PhD in American Studies (Literature, Film, and Communication) from the University of Iowa in 1981. Since then, he has held adjunct, assistant, or visiting professor positions at Brandeis University, University of California-Los Angeles, the Annenberg School for Communication at the University of Southern California, and the Newhouse School of Public Communication at Syracuse University. He is the author of a number of books on television and popular culture.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Location Station Owners/Managers Interviews consists of interviews with eleven owners and/or managers of local televisions stations across the country. All but one of the interviews were conducted by Marc, usually at the interviewee's home or office. The context of and reason for the interviews is unknown.
Arrangement of the Collection
Tapes are arranged alphabetically by interviewee.
Related Material
has numerous collections relating to radio and television. Please for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Popular culture; Radio, television, film; Arries, Les.; Bell, Alan J.; Bell, Steve.; Carey, Carl.; Clotworthy, William G., 1926-; Marc, David.; Duffy, Pat.; Epstein, Michael.; Malara, Anthony C.; Nathanson, Greg.; Primo, Albert T.; Ransom, William.; Reilly, Joseph A.; Freedom Broadcasting, Inc.; KRTH (Radio station: Los Angeles, Calif.); WGCH (Radio station: Greenwich, Conn.); WKBW-TV (Television station: Buffalo, N.Y.); New York State Broadcasters Association; Radio broadcasting -- United States -- History.; Television broadcasting -- United States -- History.; Radio stations -- Employees.; Radio stations -- Management.; Television stations -- Employees.; Television stations -- Management.; Audiocassettes.; Sound recordings.; Interviews.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from General Circulation.
Inventory
- Interviews
  - Les Arries w/DM Tape #1 of 2, 3/12/01; local_stations_001; "Osprey, FL - Both sides filled"; probably same as 003; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Les Arries w/David Marc Tape #2 of 2, 3/12/01; local_stations_002; "~20 min"; probably same as 004; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Les Arries (Tape 1 of 2), 3/12/01; local_stations_003; probably same as 001; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Les Arries (Tape 2 of 2), 3/12/01; local_stations_004; probably same as 002; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Alan J. Bell Tape #1 of 1, 6-4-01; local_stations_005; Alan J. Bell interviewed at his office, Freedom Broadcasting Inc., Irvine CA; probably same as 006; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Alan J. Bell Tape 1 of 1, 6/4/01; local_stations_006; probably same as 005; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Steve Bell Tape #1 of 2, June 5, 2001; local_stations_007; Steve Bell interviewed at his home in Pacific Palisades, CA; probably same as 009; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Steve Bell Tape #2 of 2, June 5, 2001; local_stations_008; Steve Bell interviewed at his home in Pacific Palisades, CA; probably same as 010; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Steve Bell Tape 1 of 2, 6/5/01; local_stations_009; probably same as 007; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Steve Bell Tape 2 of 2, 6/5/01; local_stations_010; probably same as 008; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Carl Bud Carey Tape #1 of 1, February 21, 2001; local_stations_011; Carl Bud Carey, Syracuse, NY; probably same as 012; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Carl Bud Carey (Tape 1 of 1), 2/21/01; local_stations_012; probably same as 011; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - William Clotworthy Tape #1 of 2, November 17, 2001; local_stations_013; William Clotworthy interviewed at his home in Asheville, NC; probably same as 015; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - William Clotworthy Tape #2 of 2, November 17, 2001; local_stations_014; William Clotworthy interviewed at his home in Asheville, NC (Side A only); probably same as 016; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - William Clotworthy Tape #1 of 2, 11/17/2001; local_stations_015; probably same as 013; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - William Clotworthy 2 of 2, 11/17/2001; local_stations_016; William Clotworthy interviewed at his home in Asheville, NC / Previous recording on this tape was not erased prior to reused; probably same as 014; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Clotworthy, undated; local_stations_017; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Pat Duffy Tape #1 of 1, 5/10/2001; local_stations_018; Pat Duffy of Radio Station KRTH-101, Los Angeles, interviewed at his office; probably same as 019; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Pat Duffy Tape 1 of 1, 5/10/01; local_stations_019; probably same as 018; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Tony Malara w/DM Tape #1 of 1, March 13, 2001; local_stations_020; Anthony C. "Tony" Malara, interviewed at his home in Siesta Key, FL; probably same as 021; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Anthony C. "Tony" Malara (Tape 1 of 1), 3/13/01; local_stations_021; probably same as 020; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Greg Nathanson Tape #1 of 2, June 6, 2001; local_stations_022; Greg Nathanson, interviewed at his home in Los Angeles; probably same as 024; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Greg Nathanson Tape #2 of 2, June 6, 2001; local_stations_023; Greg Nathanson, interviewed at his home in Los Angeles; probably same as 025; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Greg Nathanson Tape 1 of 2, 6/6/01; local_stations_024; probably same as 022; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Greg Nathanson Tape 2 of 2, 6/6/01; local_stations_025; probably same as 023; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Al Primo Tape #1 of 1, 2-2-01; local_stations_026; Al Primo, interviewed at the studios of WGCH Radio, Greenwich, CT; probably same as 027; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Al Primo (Tape 1 of 1), 2/2/01; local_stations_027; probably same as 026; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - William Ransom Tape #1 of 1, June 28, 2001; local_stations_028; William Ransom, interviewed at Ransom's office at WKBW-TV in Buffalo, NY; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Joseph A. Reilly Tape #1 of 1, 10/27/01; local_stations_029; Joseph Reilly, interviewed by David Marc, at Reilly's office, headquarters of the NY State Broadcasters Association; probably same as 030; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)
  - Joseph A. Reilly 1 of 1, 10/27/01; local_stations_030; Joseph Reilly, interviewed by David Marc, at Reilly's office, headquarters of the NY State Broadcasters Association; probably same as 029; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1)